worldmarketexplorer.com 2010-12-02

# World Market Explorer

Effective date: August 11, 2010

We value your privacy. This notice describes our privacy policy and practices. We want you to know how we collect, use, and protect information about our customers. This privacy policy will tell you:

  * What information we collect.
  * What we do with the information we collect.
  * How we may share information.
  * How you can limit contact from us.

By visiting our website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Our website may contain links to other websites operated and maintained by third parties. Other websites may also reference or link to our website. World Market is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. You should consult the individual privacy policies of those websites to determine their privacy practices before disclosing any personal information.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT

#### Information You Provide

We receive and may store any information you provide to us through our website. For example, we collect information that you provide when you place an order, register with us, send us an email, call us, sign up for our email offers or Rewards Program or enter a sweepstakes. This information may include:

  * your name;
  * your mailing address;
  * your billing address;
  * your email address;
  * your phone number; and
  * your credit card information.

It may also include any other personal or preference information you provide to us, including a record of your online product purchases. It may also include information you submit about other people, for example, the name and address of a gift recipient.

If you join our Rewards Program we will also store information about your purchases in order to calculate when you are eligible to receive a reward. 

#### Automatically Collected Information

Our web servers automatically receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us through our website. For example, when you visit the site, our system automatically recognizes your domain name and IP address(es), date and time of visits, the type of browser you use, the website from which your visit originated, page visits, time spent on web pages, and other similar traffic data. No personal information about you is revealed in this process. This information may be used by us to operate the website and to provide general statistics regarding the use of the website.

#### Cookies

Our website uses "cookies" to customize your shopping experience or to keep track of your shopping cart. "Cookies" are pieces of information that are sent to your browser and stored in your computer's hard drive. Cookies enable us to more easily communicate and interact with you. You may disallow cookies through your web browser and still browse and shop on our website.

#### Information from Other Sources

We may obtain information about you from outside sources and combine it with your account information. For example, we may purchase commercially available demographics and other marketing information from third parties to help us better serve you or inform you about products or services that we think will be of interest to you. We sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily. Finally, we may also purchase lists containing your personal information (e.g., postal address, phone number, email address) for advertising and marketing purposes.

### USE OF INFORMATION

#### Personal Information

We may use your personal information to process or follow up with transactions initiated on the website or through our customer service department to let you know about products and promotions that we think may be of interest to you or to notify you when you have earned a reward under our Reward Program. We may share information provided by you directly or through cookies with companies that provide support services to us such as a transaction processor, printer, mailing house, or web host or with companies that help us market our products and services. These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. These companies are not authorized to use the information we share with them for any other purpose, or to share that information with anyone other than the company and its agents.

#### Disclosure to Successors

We may disclose your personal information to any actual or potential successor-in-interest of ours, such as a company that is seeking to acquire us, the website, or the business and activities carried on via the website.

#### Aggregate Information

We may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Under California law, you have the right to request and receive information from retailers concerning any third parties who have received personal information about you from the retailers for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. Any such requests for information from us can be made by sending an email to [privacy@cpwm.com](mailto:privacy@cpwm.com) or by calling us at 1-877-967-5362.

### DISCLOSURES ORDERED BY LAW

We may disclose information you provide to our website when we believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law; when it is necessary to identify, contact, bring, or defend legal action against persons or entities that we believe may be causing harm to you, our company, or third parties; and when necessary, to protect or defend our rights or property.

### PROTECTING CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

This is a general audience website; it is not directed at children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from any child under the age of 13 at this website, nor do we send email correspondence to anyone who tells us that they are under the age of 13.

### HOW YOU CAN LIMIT CONTACT FROM US

#### Emails

If you provide our company with your email address, you may receive emails from us. If you do not want to receive marketing or promotional emails from us, please email us at [emailunsubscribe@cpwm.com](mailto:emailunsubscribe@cpwm.com), or you may let us know by logging in to "My Profile" and indicating your preference. Please call 1-877-967-5362 if you have further questions about our email unsubscribe process. Your request will be handled promptly, although you may still receive marketing communications that were already in process prior to receipt of your request.

#### Other Mailings

If you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us that may include information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at 1-877-967-5362. Your request will be handled promptly, although you may still receive marketing communications that were already in process prior to receipt of your request.

#### Correcting or Updating Information

If you have registered with us, you may review for accuracy and update your profile information online by logging in to "My Profile" using your email address and password and editing your information accordingly. The length of time we keep your information will vary depending on the nature of your transactions on the website and personal information involved. We have retention standards that meet customer service, legal and regulatory needs. For these reasons, we may keep your information beyond the end of your relationship with us. When your information is no longer required, we will dispose of it with appropriate care and diligence.

### SECURITY

We have appropriate physical, electronic, and procedural security safeguards to protect and secure the information we collect. Nonetheless, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to or from our website, and you do so at your own risk.

Our website uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), a protocol developed for transmitting private documents via the Internet. SSL uses a cryptographic system that uses two keys to encrypt data including your personal credit information. SSL technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions. 

### UPDATES TO THIS POLICY

Updates and changes to this privacy policy will be posted on our website and will be effective from the date they are posted, unless otherwise noted. New policies will apply to all current and past users of the website and supersede any inconsistent policies previously in effect.

### YOUR CONSENT

By using our website, you consent to our use of information that is collected or submitted as described in this online privacy policy. This privacy policy is subject to change, so we encourage you to review it periodically.

* * *
